Tufts Daily UP029
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Daily, 1994; UP029.015; 2.4 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 126 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Daily, 1994 November 30; UP029.015.025.00052 (Volume 25)
    Dewick, MacPhie will undergo major renovation over summer. CSL [Committee on Student Life] inept in its review of the TCU [Tufts Community Unioin] constitution. What is the Hanukkah thing? Solid start for women's hoops [basketball].
  - Tufts Daily, 1994 December 01; UP029.015.025.00053 (Volume 25)
    Tufts Amalgamates to celebrate tenth anniversary next semester; Video store may replace Jumbo Scoops, new cafe to open in fall. [John] DiBiaggio details his vision for Tufts 2002. Colloquium discusses prize for international relations students. Disagreements with the new Constitution. Tufts Amalgamates to celebrate tenth anniversary next semester. Ice hockey team blown out by Army. Jumbo sailors end season, [Mark] Mendelblatt finishes third.
  - Tufts Daily, 1994 December 02; UP029.015.025.00054 (Volume 25)
    [Administration and Budget, Committee on 1994-95] Senate will introduce the capstone program. Sunday morning will mark the opening of new Hillel building. Senate will introduce the Capstone Program. Women's basketball looking for balance. Jumbos [Men's basketball] look for a Maine sweep. Men's basketball is driving at 55. Swimmers score a win. [Kara] Murph: an athlete for all seasons. Sailing team gives annual awards.
  - Tufts Daily, 1994 December 05; UP029.015.025.00055 (Volume 25)
    Dedication ceremony held for opening of new Hillel Center. Workshop to discuss health, safety issues. Crafts Center exists one-quarter century. Maine sweep! [Men's basketball]. Record-setting performance by [Dan] Ragsdale stuns the Polar Bears. Browning to match for Jumbo shooters. Colby, Bowdoin sent packing. Women's [basketball] frontcourt play key to victories.
  - Tufts Daily, 1994 October 18; UP029.015.040.00009 (Volume UP029 Shared 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 1994 November 11; UP029.015.040.00010 (Volume UP029 Shared 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 1994 November 30; UP029.015.040.00011 (Volume UP029 Shared 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 1994 December 07; UP029.015.040.00047 (Volume UP029 Shared 2)
    The object ID for this issue does not reflect its current location because it was ingested before a paper copy was found, October, 2008.
  - Tufts Daily, 1994 October 19; UP029.015.DO.00001
  - Tufts Daily, 1994 December 06; UP029.015.DO.00002
  - Tufts Daily, 1994 December 08; UP029.015.DO.00004
  - Tufts Daily, 1994 December 09; UP029.015.DO.00005
  - Tufts Daily, 1994 December 12; UP029.015.DO.00006
- Tufts Daily, 1995; UP029.016; 2.4 Linear Feet; 65 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 January 18; UP029.016.025.00056 (Volume 25)
    [Administration 1994/95] Galvin appointed Dean of Fletcher School.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 January 20; UP029.016.025.00057 (Volume 25)
    Tilton is designated as an all-freshmen dorm. Faulty electrical equipment is the cause of uphill's power shutdown. Parking situation has shown improvement. Constitution to be the major focus of senators for the spring semester. Jumbo [Men's basketball] reserves grab spotlight, Vikings sing the blues. Women's basketball suffers a loss. Swimmers get ready for their second half.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 January 24; UP029.016.025.00058 (Volume 25)
    Senate adopts new constitution. Weekend confrontation results in three arrests. Experimental College organizes [John] DiBiaggio's address to freshmen. Senate creates pocket guide to Tufts. [Barry] Zimman remembered. [Men's basketball] [Chad] Onofrio to [Chris] McMahon dunk spells lights out for Falcons. Women [basketball] drop one to Wellesley. Women's track works together. Tufts ski team off to excellent start.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 January 26; UP029.016.025.00059 (Volume 25)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Fraternity Rush 1995; Changes implemented for next year in housing, residential life. Peer advocates will aid in disciplinary process. Legendary jazz musician Dave Brubeck will headline concert. Fraternity Rush 1995. [Robert] McMahon, [Rich] LaFauci earn awards. [Ice Hockey] New York battle opens season.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 January 30; UP029.016.025.00060 (Volume 25)
    [John] DiBiaggio's speech to freshmen highlights University priorities. Mail fraud results in student suspensions. Yearbook is plagued by lack of support from graduating class. [men's basketball] [Chris] McMahon and [Chris] Toglia become friendly foes. Men's hoops rams Suffolk, 97-70. Women's hoops takes out UMass. [women's basketball] Tufts whips UMass despite sloppy plays.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 January 31; UP029.016.025.00061 (Volume 25)
    [David] Brinker presents TCU [Tufts Community Union] with new resolutions about student rights. Student is disciplined for housing violation. [Dining Services] Committee will work to institute off-campus points for the future. Tufts senior to appear on Jeopardy!. More Thoughts on the All-Freshmen Residence Hall. a steel drum quickly. Big Brothers at Tufts. Men's track victorious at Bowdoin. [Men's basketball] Babson poses challenge to Jumbos. Swim team aided by their winter training. [Administration 1994/95] Brinker presents Tufts Community Union with new resolutions about student rights.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 01; UP029.016.025.00062 (Volume 25)
    [Alpha Omicron Pi] Anti-Greel chalkings are spotted on campus; Renovations will begin soon on Michael chemistry research lab. Anti-Greek chalkings are spotted on campus. New professor of public service joins the Lincoln Filene Center. Professor knew Newt [Gingrich] back when. Women's Center good resource. [Men's basketball] Tufts' Big Three strikes again. [Men's basketball] 'D' was the key to beating Babson. Women's basketball disposes of Williams. [Women's basketball] [Jodi] Beach storms Ephs for 29 points.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 02; UP029.016.025.00063 (Volume 25)
    [John] DiBiaggio discusses agenda for trustees, fundraising campaign. New athletic center for disabled may be built at Tufts. The President's Message. Attitude Adjustment, Anyone?. Comments on the Chief's Speech. Off-campus housing has many attractions. [Men's soccer] [Ralph] Ferrigno sweeps coaching honors. Men's, women's squash drop three against tough squads. [Damon] Adams named '95 football captain.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 03; UP029.016.025.00064 (Volume 25)
    Renovations of Bush, MacPhie, and Dewick to start in summer. [David] Brinker will deliver address this Sunday. Students will protest Mitsubishi's destruction of the world's forests. [Elizabeth] Eisenstein named Energy Manager. Student interest in religion and spiritualism on the rise at Tufts. [Tufts Swimming] Coach Nancy Bigelow scores her 100th win. Jumbos [ice hockey] roar to eighth straight. [Men's basketball] Men fall to Lord Jeffs, await Hamilton.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 06; UP029.016.025.00065 (Volume 25)
    Academic Resource Center; The ARC is for everyone to use; P.3. CSL [Committee on Student Life] approves a new draft of Constitution. Trustee [William S.] Cummings will speak to students on Thursday afternoon. Winter's first major storm leaves behind snow and frigid weather. The ARC [Academic Resource Center] is for everyone to use. [Men's basketball] Snowed Under!. [Men's basketball] [Chris] McMahon: There can be only one.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 07; UP029.016.025.00066 (Volume 25)
    Senators request that faculty meetings be made more open. Faculty reviews plans for fundraising drive. TCU [Tufts Community Union] President David Brinker gives speech on state of Senate. State of the Senate Address. Quiz show wizardry. Jumbos [ice hockey] divine in their ninth win.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 08; UP029.016.025.00067 (Volume 25)
    Uncleared ice leaves sidewalks dangerous. TEMS [Tufts Emergency Medical Services] adopts new certification requirements, improves services. Student reaction to Safety Shuttle performance mixed. LCS [Leonard Carmichael Society] offers way to fix the world. Men's hoops spanks Engineers. [Women's basketball] Tufts stomps on Mount Holyoke.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 09; UP029.016.025.00068 (Volume 25)
    Pep rally for basketball games expected to boost school spirit. Religious sect grows in Tufts community. Students voice their Opposition to Fraternities. [Sol] Gittleman's Interdisciplinary Infidelities. Squash team tumbles to Engineers.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 10; UP029.016.025.00069 (Volume 25)
    Trustees will meet on campus this weekend. LCS [Leonard Carmichael Society] hopes blood drive will aid in upping the regional blood supply. Discussion of trustee luncheon is focus of Sunday Senate meeting. Hockey goes, we lose. [Men's basketball] Tufts gest the runs, just survives. [Men's basketball] A few very good men. [Men's basketball] Assitant coach [Al] Coccoluto rules. Prep star, courageous 31-year-old, highlight wild night. [All-College Council] Discussion of trustee luncheon is focus of Sunday Senate meeting.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 13; UP029.016.025.00070 (Volume 25)
    [Men's basketball] Yes!. E-mail account allows students to comment on Health Services. Trustee [William Cummings] speaks about his business successes. Oxfam opens its doors ready to work for a successful semester. Boston Public Library more than just research center. [Men's basketball] Tufts clinches a weekend victory William Ephmen. Trinity whips rug out from under women's hoops, 78-63. Beach nets her 1,000th point in women's [basketball] loss to Trinity Saturday. Tufts hockey keeps on stomping.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 14; UP029.016.025.00071 (Volume 25)
    Date set for vote on TCU [Tufts Community Union] document. Trustees meet, set budget. Senate rejects Mitsubishi protest, passes two education resolutions. Dining Services director speaks to senators on plans for Dewick, MacPhie renovations. "Rave" Atempted at Tufts. Senatorial Power Play. Tufts Sex Talk leads celebration of National Condom Week 1995. [Men's track] Tufts' runners second. Jumbos [hockey] set sights on top-ranked Corsairs as travel to Dartmouth. Hockey team wins two as streak grows longer. Tufts sex talk leads celebration of National condom week 1995.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 15; UP029.016.025.00072 (Volume 25)
    All residences may be wired for cable and internet this summer. Merger of Deaconess, NEMC [New England Medical Center] being debated. Renowned historian [Doris Kearns Goodwin] will lecture about private lives of presidents. SeniorFund looking for a few good seniors to take over. A Tale of Two Halves: Jumbos [women's basketball] come to life in 67-48 win. One great victory, but one terrible defeat.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 16; UP029.016.025.00073 (Volume 25)
    Police report a lower crime rate on campus during fall semester. MTV group to appear on campus next week. Two professors [Juliet Fuhrman, Carole Martin] are honored with grants from Mellon Foundation. Ambassador [Maleeha Lodhi] to speak in Cabot. Wind Ensemble meets Eliot Pearson scholars. Hockey team derailed by UMass. [Men's basketball] Marksmanship earns Onofrio national title.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 17; UP029.016.025.00074 (Volume 25)
    [Peggy] Barrett led discussion on policy for sexual harassment at Tufts. Students want kosher meals at dining halls. Senate will discuss Mitsubishi resolution at upcoming session. Sol Gittleman talks about World War II, stresses its significance. Community Health Program is unique. [Ice Hockey] Incomplete effort yields 2-2 tie. Women's swim team is at championships. Men's basketball team surging.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 21; UP029.016.025.00075 (Volume 25)
    [Alpha Omicron Pi] Greek housees say Walnut Hill is not negotiating rent rates fairly. Greek houses say Walnut Hill is not negotiating rent rates fairly. [Tisch] Library construction is going as scheduled. 'Visions of the future' is EPIIC [Education for Public Inquiry and International Citizenship]'s symposium theme. A Dorm for You, A Dorm for Me... TASA [Tufts Association of Southern Asians] works to increase Tufts students' knowledge of events. Lady Jumbos [women's basketball] lose to [Katie] Hubert-led Panthers. Middlebury no match for men [basketball].
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 22; UP029.016.025.00076 (Volume 25)
    ZBT [Zeta Beta Tau] and AEPi [Alpha Epsilon Pi] will move into on-campus houses by next fall. Campus wiring will speed up Emerald. [David] Brinker presents proposal for student Bill of Rights to Senate. [Squash] Men split, women lose two as the teams approach postseason play. [Men's Track] [James] Lavalle and [Damon] Adams pace men's track team to fourth place finish.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 23; UP029.016.025.00077 (Volume 25)
    New Intramural basketball court in Cousens Gym to be built soon. [Joycelyn] Elders will speak to students next week. Board of Trustees approves policy for second fraternity rush period. Circuit breaker fails, uphill loses hot water. Religion department rules. Beach and seniors exit Jumbodome as winners [Women's basketball]. Judges rule, Tufts [Men's basketball] punished. Women's track places sixth at Saturday's meet.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 24; UP029.016.025.00078 (Volume 25)
    Plans for video store are axed. South Hall locks will switch to all ID card access for security. Senators will address issue of student rights. Women's swimmers finish fifth in New England championships. Playoff outlook for men's [basketball] team clouded from Wednesday's loss.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 27; UP029.016.025.00079 (Volume 25)
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 February 28; UP029.016.025.00080 (Volume 25)
    Tufts student's thesis develops into a book. Resolution calls for card key dorm locks. NCAA [National Collegiate Athletic Association] basketball tournament game will be played at bentley. Senators approve boycott of [Mitsubishi] company. EPIIC [Education for Public Inquiry and International Citizenship] celebrates its tenth anniversary with symposium on '20/20 visions of the future'. Tufts student's thesis develops into a book. Ex College panel discusses the use of computers in education. Men's track earns tight victory at meet. Women's hoops earns ECAC [Eastern College Athletic Conference] bid. Behruoz Abedian. Panel discusses the use of computers in education.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 March 01; UP029.016.025.00081 (Volume 25)
    Residential Life head position still unfilled. Major drug seizure results in the expulsion of Tufts student. Emerald system crashes after hard drive failure on Monday. Oxford program takes five Tufts sophomores. Wacky comments abound on the Dewick/MacPhie comment board. Cheaper phone rates from peers. [Men's] Hockey set to take Skidmore. Embarrassment and shame like no other [at the National Collegiate Athletic Association tournament].
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 March 02; UP029.016.025.00082 (Volume 25)
    [Joycelyn] Elders talks on health education and gender. [Doris Kearns] Goodwins to address Class of 1995 at graduation. TCU [Tufts Community Union] commuter representative stands to lose voting priviledges. Finalists for Wendell Phillips award named. GAMMA's lectures continue on. Brown: just another Tufts [Men's basketball] pro. Jumbos hit the skids [men's hockey]. Wait till next year for women's basketball.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 March 03; UP029.016.025.00083 (Volume 25)
    [American diabetes association] Fourth annual tour de cure; [Men's] Hockey team saved, will play past 1997. [Men's Basketball] Hoopsters humbled. Senate will discuss card key locks, student empowerment at meeting. Students say they were framed in poster scam. [mens] Swimmers are stellar in New England meet.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 March 06; UP029.016.025.00084 (Volume 25)
    Student receives suspension for fraudulent use of campus phone. Tufts Medical School starts MBA program. [Education for Public Inquiry and International Citizenship] EPIIC programs provide a look at the world in 2020. Attendance at men's and women's games unequal. 'Daily' sends TEMS [Tufts Emergency Medical Service] to hospital in Saturday's [men's] basketball game.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 March 07; UP029.016.025.00085 (Volume 25)
    Aidekman Arts Center [1994/95]. Art exhibit, "In Light of Our Relection." Sophomores have two weeks to pick a major. Faculty votes to increase the World Civilizations options. Proposal for 'Pachyderm' on disk announced to Senate. Commuter Senator should have a vote. Men's and Women's squash send competitors to national tourney.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 March 08; UP029.016.025.00086 (Volume 25)
    Poorly attended forum looks at student [em]power[ment]. Health Service pursues changes following recent quality review. Wendell Phillips [Award] finalists compete for oratory award. Religious life at Tufts since 1852 changed more than the students. Successful turn around for Tufts [Women's basketball]. Men's track takes fourth at ECAC [Eastern College Athletic Conference].
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 March 09; UP029.016.025.00087 (Volume 25)
    Sarah McGinley wins Wendell Phillips Award. DiBiaggio says student opinions are important to the University. Decision on Health services has not yet been reached. Beach garners end of [women's basketball] season honors. They will hold their heads high [men's basketball].
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 March 10; UP029.016.025.00088 (Volume 25)
    [American Cancer Society] Proceeds from Greek jam donated; [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Eighth annual Greek Jam tonight; Academic Computing Services (ACS) 1994-95. Problems abound Emerald, ACS attempts to restore service. ELBO [Elections Board] is irresponsible in handling of voting. TCU [Tufts Community Union] constitution fails to pass, not enough students cast votes. Problems abound with Emerald, ACS [Academic Computing Services] attempts to restore service.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 March 13; UP029.016.025.00089 (Volume 25)
    [Provost Sol] Gittleman's trip to South Africa may have implications for Tufts. Faculty debates CFS [Faculty committee on Fraternity and sorority life] proposal to disband. Assistant hoops catch Pat Skerry not afraid of next step. Gold medalist [Brad Lewis] will speak at Tufts.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 March 14; UP029.016.025.00090 (Volume 25)
    Motion for banning CFS [Committee on Fraternities and Sororities] passes at meeting. Senators set date for new vote on revised constitution. Administrators support hiring new Religion faculty members. Classroom doors thrown open, [college without grades]. GSW closes tour in providence [men's track]
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 March 15; UP029.016.025.00091 (Volume 25)
    Condom distribution, safe sex are focus of Tufts Sex Talk discussion. [Eva] Hoffman uses grant to create computer study guide. Services committee continues its projects.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 March 16; UP029.016.025.00092 (Volume 25)
    Two political science professors are hired. Faculty vote on amendment to dissolve CFS [Committee on Fraternities and Sororities] invalid. EX college celebrates 30 years at Tufts University this month. Great way to spend a Saturday.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 March 17; UP029.016.025.00093 (Volume 25)
    Environment will be focus of conference. Opening up the classroom looks at the role of the grading system. Men's baseball prepares for a challenging nine days.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 March 27; UP029.016.025.00094 (Volume 25)
    ALBO [Allocations Board] proposes new rules that will cut funding to TCU [Tufts Community Union] groups. Things are looking good for Gus.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 March 28; UP029.016.025.00095 (Volume 25)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Fraternaties receive houses; Phi Sigma Sigma will be dissolved this year. Faulty Emerald system replaced for second time by new machine. Chris McMahon earns team All-American title (basketball). Women's softball got a break; return with sunny 9-3 record.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 March 29; UP029.016.025.00096 (Volume 25)
    Funds from Elders lecture will not go to charity due to errors. Provost gives opinion on student influence. Men's track team to start season at home. Tenning plays close to perfection. [Allocations Board] Senate cuts funding for instuctors of student groups, p. 1, 11.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 March 30; UP029.016.025.00097 (Volume 25)
    Blues guitarist B.B.King signs to headline Spring Fling show.; [Admissions] DiBiaggio comments on Tufts' admissions. pp. 1, 9.; Softball beats Boston Univeristy, 2-1.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 April 01; UP029.016.026.00001 (Volume 26)
    EPIIC [Education for Public Inquiry and International Citizenship] to host more dull stuff. Emerald exorcised; daemon the culprit. [David] Brinker amidst guilt. Acts of God result in TCU [Tufts Community Union] Constitution passing. Vertically challenged win house. US's ugliest feminist [Chris Mynn] discusses dating. Beach, McMahon regain eligibility. [Basketball] Team wins game. New basketball court to be built short of regulations, says [Rocky] Carzo.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 April 03; UP029.016.026.00002 (Volume 26)
    Tufts ranks high in award competition. Speech Society sponsors debate with Oxford students in Chapel. Tufts trustee [Dr. Stephen B. Blount] will speak on social justice and medicine. Ex [Experimental] College members party hard. Softball team streaks to its eighth straight win after victory over BU. Lacrosse topples Mt. Holyoke in royal start.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 April 04; UP029.016.026.00003 (Volume 26)
    Date on Page 1 is incorrect. Classes for World Civilizations are being considered by faculty. Senators display their immaturity, insecurity. Senators pass budgets for all but two student groups. Then students receive Seniors Awards. School spirit and Division III athletics become the hot topic. Students to have opportunity to view special shadows Thursday. Jumbos [Baseball] number one in Division III region. Women's track springs forward.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 April 05; UP029.016.026.00004 (Volume 26)
    NOW [National Organization for Women] president gives speech on feminism as part of college tour. Tufts trustee [Dr. Stephen Blount] speaks on the future of medicine. Senate guarantees commuters' voting rights in revised charter. Starve yourself for a good cause. Men's track takes first in meet. Men's lacrosse aims for success. March Madness contest results.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 April 06; UP029.016.026.00005 (Volume 26)
    Dr. Ali Mazrui will speak on UN [United Nations] issues. Tufts associate history professor [Dr. John L. Brooke] is recipient of the Bancroft Prize. Tufts and affirmative action. Multicultural curricula: Where are we going? A whole lotta famine going on. Freshmen are drinking like fish. Crew falls to defending champs. Soccer team honored. Baseball 16th in the nation; [Affirmative Action] Tufts and affirmative action, p. 3, 11.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 April 07; UP029.016.026.00006 (Volume 26)
    Proposal aims to cut $20 billion in student financial aid funding. TCU [Tufts Community Union] course evaluation guide has a new format. Noted rabbi [Lawrence Kushner] will visit Hillel Center. Programs attempt to end domestic violence. [Baseball] Two inning plan snares victory. Amherst, Conn. College, cloud postseason picture for Jumbos [Men's Tennis]; Women's lacrosse chills Wellesley; [Adler, Emily-chair of Edu. Committee] TCU course evaluation guide has a new format. p. 1, 10.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 April 10; UP029.016.026.00007 (Volume 26)
    George Wallace is scheduled to perform in spring comedy show. Tufts alumna [Vanessa Kirsch] receives civic leadership award. Drama director [Professor William Sun] wins NEH [National Endowment for the Humanities] grant. Men's track dominates at meet.
  - Tufts Daily, 1995 April 11; UP029.016.026.00008 (Volume 26)